Every time the rain no longer falls,
and I see the sky,
I think back to when I was
a child Who could only cry
Blindly chasing after him
I fell far behind my only
thought One day I will be
stronger Bridery and gratitude
Fading with the wind Am I
stronger now than I was before?
Or as weak as back then?
I don't know for sure But until
I do, my voyage will not end!
No matter what's next,
I'm walking straight ahead
So let's go, there's nothing
that can stop us now!
Though time's all on our side,
we'll never let it pull us down
And we may fall,
but we'll always keep on standing There's
no way anything will take what I hold
dear away from me The voices inside me
push me to keep surviving I'll go on,
I'll get through,
no matter what I gotta do
The fiercest of the ball can
pour upon me I don't care why
in the world would I turn back
So let's go There's nothing that
can stop us now Though time's
not on our side We'll never let it
pull us down And we may fall But
we'll always keep on standing There's
no way anything Will take what
I hold dear away from me I know
the future's there for us to see?
What's going on?
Where's the picture?
We want to see the war!
Hurry and get it fixed!
It looks like they're having problems
with the video transponder snails.
Maybe they got blown up in
the crossfire or something.
Is it true that the Navy and Whitebeard
have some kind of deal worked out?
Did Whitebeard really sell out his allies?
We all want to know how
the war's going to end.
Come on.
The whole world's at stake.
Just when I thought the Navy
couldn't sink any lower.
It's been nothing but a sideshow till now.
The only reason we came back to
Sabo Odi was to watch the war.
Of course the snail's malfunctioning.
Are you really buying that? What?
You mean you don't?
Of course not.
What are you, stupid?
There's only one way the Navy
would allow that feed to cut out.
They don't want the world to
see what they're about to do.
You okay, Captain Barney? Go away!
Just shut up!
Whitebeard sold out as allies?
What a load of crap.
The man's a living legend because
all us pirates respect him.
Let's set sail, Beppo.
Aye, aye, Captain!
You with us, Sean Berets?
Yes, sir, you heard me right.
Seems like there's no chance
of recovering the signal.
I have no idea what's happening
at Marineford right now.
Meteor Volcano!
They've got nowhere to run.
Now we'll melt that ice!
And drown them all.
It's a worm.
No, no it's not a birdie?
The Lama's boiling the sea!
Hurry and get on the ice!
Hey, look!
They're blocking us in here!
We've got to be able to
take down this wall somehow!
Ah! Ah!
Ah!
White beard.
How is it still standing
after a shot from Pops?
What is that thing made of?
All right, let's hit him
where it really hurts.
That bastard aimed
straight for the Moby Dick.
We've got to put out the fire.
All hands on Dick.
Grab a bucket and put it out, damn it.
We can't let her sink.
It just won't be the same sailing
with Ace again without the Moby Dick.
Whitebeard, watch your
legacy go up in flames!
The Moby Dick, it's...
it's gone!
No!
Damn those monsters!
That ship was the only home we knew!
Damn it!
Don't give up now!
The Voby Dick has been carrying
the white-bit pirates for decades!
I'm sorry, old friend.
We've got to get to the plaza
before this gets any worse!
The plan is working
perfectly, so we'll proceed!
Phase two is the immediate
execution of Portgas D. Ace!
We gotta get up there
and stop them but how
we're completely trapped no there's still
a way out Just look ahead and see the
path that oars made
but that's like a death
trap that's exactly where The Navy's
expecting us to go the more we think the more
time we waste yeah it's The only way we
can save Ace even if it means our death?
Ace!
Strawhead.
We're right here behind you, kid.
They're running straight into
the line of fire. Not yet.
Let them get as close as possible.
Now!
There's only one way in and one way out.
Where else is the Navy going
to point their cannons?
It's a slaughterhouse!
Fire!
Strawboy, no!
Luffy!
Ah!
Ah! Ah!
How is little Oars still alive?
Did nobody check his pulse? Ah!
Get away from me! Ah! Oars!
I will die till you're safe.
Ors, no!
Get back in the fight.
Even now?
I'm ready.
No more falling in the sea, all right?
Honestly, you're too reckless.
Prepare to open fire, men.
No!
Ours, stop!
We gotta do something,
and we gotta do it fast!
There's no time left!
They already issued
the order to kill Lace!
Yes, but we need a strategy.
Team Bay, I need a favor from you.
Well, he's a tough one.
He's just about dead. Keep shooting!
Save your bullets, boys.
I'll finish him off.
Admiral!
We've dealt with enough setbacks.
We need to get this execution on the road.
A headshot seems appropriate,
quick, easy, and 100 % effective.
Motion, power, shoulders roll!
I see.
So you found a way up.
You've done quite well, son of dragon.
You're standing tall now.
Ah, youth.
So much fire.
That's Straw Hat Luffy who
got thrown over the wall.
He's his brother.
Well done, brat.
I do respect your tenacity,
kid, but it's not enough.
That's right.
It's a fluke.
You got this.
Far and you're too
green to go any further.
Whatever gives you the
idea, you can defeat us?
He and his brother are two of a kind.
They just dive right in
without even thinking.
Ors, stay put.
I need your help one more time.
Sure, Bob.
Geoise, the trump card. Yes, sir.
Get ready to move, everyone.
We're charging straight into the plaza.
Go, go, stay. Mr. Butler!
Now for second gear!
Straight to Ace!
I don't have time to fight these guys!
Hmm, trying to sneak by us, huh?
Ah, you almost made it.
Get ready, men. Sir!
Now do it!
Oh,
my God.
Who did that?
You bastard!
I thought it would be advantageous
to have you here for the battle,
since you hold a grudge
against Whitebeard.
Curse you, Crocodile!
No way!
What's going on?
I thought I'd have a chance to show off.
Just a short while ago, Crocodile
was trying to murder Whitebeard.
Wonder what transpired to
make him change his mind.
I can kill that old dying
buzzard whenever I feel like it,
but as for right now, I'm not
going to let you taste victory,
you and your crooked operation.
Hey pal do you remember me it's so
flamingo first you turned me down and now
you want to team up with whitebeard
you got some nerve
playing me like that!
Don't be foolish i'm not
teaming up with anybody!
Either way you're giving my
friendship a cold shoulder!
I can't say i appreciate that!
Deal with it.
Those two are distracting everybody else!
Now's my chance!
Hey, Straw Hats!
You're mine!
Die!
Better get out of my way!
Yes!
Not another step, Straw Hat!
Your temper tantrum ends
right now! Move it! Change!
Moon move!
Iron body!
Smash!
Control!
Iron body!
Blast!
Don't let him come any closer!
Admiral Sakazuki said...
Damn it!
That hurts!
I still owe your grandfather a favor,
Straw Hat, but you've left me no choice.
You chose to risk your life.
You've got to face the music.
You fiend!
I won't let you hurt my darling!
Admiral!
Oh, crap!
Whitebeard's 1st Division
commander, Marco!
Thanks, buddy.
You saved me.
Ah, don't mention it, pal.
There are three invaders in the plaza.
They're using their Devil Fruit
powers to go straight over the walls.
Come on, everybody.
Don't stop swearing
until you get the horse!
We have to get to the plaza,
no matter what it takes!
They really think they can get to us, huh?
Guard the gap and don't let them through!
Sir!
They've got nothing to lose now that
we've sunk the ice in their ships.
Talk about an easy target.
Now fire away while we
still have the chance!
Grab the hose and get on board!
It's another pirate ship
sir we have a problem
another coated pirate
ships about to enter the
bayonets coming fast
you've got to be kidding me
it must have been hidden
underwater the entire time?
We caught those puns off guard.
I never said they had
sunk all of our ships.
It looks like a battle boat!
And it's heading straight
for us at full speed!
No!
Whitebeard!
Now sink that thing!
Drop it like the Moby Dick!
Cease fire!
This ship is too fast!
Aim your firing oars! What?
Oars the giant?
Too late, Sengoku.
Everybody better!
That's insane.
He plugged the ship right out of the bay.
This is bad.
They've broken through
the encircling walls.
We made it to the plaza, guys.
Ace!
Ace is right there!
Let's burn the headquarters down!
Hold on, Ace!
We're coming!
Hmm. Impressive.
That space could barely
fit one ship through.
Yet here we are with a
boat full of pirates.
The walls were supposed to trap them, but
they might end up trapping us instead.
That's enough!
He just won't give up.
Lucky break.
We got here right on time.
Sit tight, Ace.
Yeah, we did it!
The platform!
Ace is on the platform!
We can -
Oh, Snow! No!
Save Ace for me, guys!
Don't let them kill him!
Oh, horse, why?
Oh, my God.
It's Whitebeard!
Whitebeard has entered the plaza!
My sons, please, stay back.
Screaming.
Listen up, pirates!
Bring Ace to safety!
And once you're done with
that, destroy the Navy!
Are you with me, Garp?
Yeah.
I fear we can't hold back anymore.
This battle may be our last.
Thank you.